# Dhaker SALAH

# Software engineer/ Web developer

+21655635707 | dhakersalah15@gmail.com | Tunis, Tunisia | github.com/DhakerSalah | linkedin.com/in/dhakersalah

# **ABOUT ME**

Achieving the career of your dreams is not impossible when you know where to start...

As a certified scrum web developer participated in and developed a wide range of projects, I am a computer engineer specializing in software engineering. My training is proof of my autonomy and my adaptability, and my professional experiences have allowed me to develop my critical sense. On the personal side, I am a rather communicative, sociable, attentive and reliable person. I have an active life position and I am driven by a strong curiosity to learn, hardworking, rigorous, available and I have a good sense of direction.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Web developer (Python, NodeJS / ReactJS) & mobile developer (React Native)

(Jul 2023 - Today)

SBG TECHELECTRO, Tunis, Tunisia

- Analyze of needs.
- Design and implement models and services for an existing project.
- Change a non-relational database (NoSQL) to a relational database (SQL) by migrating data and changing functions
  according to the new architecture.
- Work with Google Cloud Storage (GCS).
- Deploy projects and databases on Azure and DigitalOcean.
- Software versioning (Git).
- Working with Github actions (CI/CD).
- Test endpoints after migration and consume APIs.
- Develop new functions in code as needed.
- Working in Ubuntu and Virtual machine (VM).
- Working with Nginx and Gunicorn.
- Working with SSL Certificate and HTTPS Redirect (From HTTP to HTTPS).
- Working with prisma ORM
- Develop mobile applications for Android and IOS include modules for push notifications and BLE (Bluetooth Low Energy)

#### Backend developer (Python Django)

(Oct 2022 - May 2023)

# Carnelian Digital Innovation, Tunis, Tunisia

- Analyse of needs.
- Recommend and implement technical solutions according to deadlines, budget and human resources.
- Test in an acceptance environment and validate with the whole team the functionalities put in place.
- Working with Celery, Redis and Elasticsearch.
- Security and access managment.
- Database administration (PostgreSQL).
- Software versioning (Git).
- Evolution in agile environment (scrum).

# **FORMATION**

National Engineering Diploma in Software Engineering

Private polytechnic school of Monastir, Monastir | 2019 - 2022

Fundamental license in computer management

Higher Institute of Management of Sousse, Sousse | 2016 - 2019

# **SKILLS**

#### **FRONT END**

# • HTML, CSS

- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS

#### **BACK END**

- Django (Python)
- Flask (Python)
- NodeJS (JavaScript)

## **MOBILE**

React native

#### **DATABASES**

- MySQL (SQL)
- PostgreSQL (SQL)
- MongoDB (No SQL)

# **INTERNSHIPS**

### **CLEVERTECH FRANCE** (07 Feb 2022 – 08 Jul 2022)

- Development of a web & mobile application for restaurant management (DJANGO REACT JS REACT NATIVE AGILE SCRUM – AZURE).
- Generate automatic qr code.
- Integrate the Twilio and the SendGrid tools.

#### **GROUPE FLORUS, Tunis** | (01 Aug 2021 – 31 Aug 2021)

 Development of a web application for users management (ANGULAR – SPRING BOOT – AGILE SCRUM).

#### **CARTHAGE SOLUTION**, **Tunis** | (10 Août 2020 – 10 Sept 2020)

- Development of a web application for company management (HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, MYSQL).
- Create a client project with WordPress.

# **DEV-GX, Tunis** | (11 Fév 2019 – 10 Mai 2019)

 Design and development of a web application of human resources management (ANGULAR – LARAVEL).

#### **SANCELLA, Tunis** | (01 Juil 2018 – 31 Juil 2018)

• Development of a leave web application in PHP.

# **CERTIFICATES**

#### > Coursera - IBM

(IBM Full Stack Developer)

https://coursera.org/verify/professional-cert/QFAW7RVFJB35

#### Coursera - Meta

(Meta Backend Developer)

https://coursera.org/verify/professional-cert/BB6YY4TNTBRC

#### SCRUM study

(Scrum Fundamentals Certified)

https://www.scrumstudy.com/certification/verify?type=SFC&number=891020

#### LinkedIn Learning

(Become a Software Developer)

https://www.linkedin.com/learning/certificates/0feaea34dd19fff06127deb790b471769a0d68b5e13e137116237ff5fc853f6f

#### **➢** IBM

(IBM Academic Certificate exam for Big Data Engineer)

#### Microsoft

(HTML MTA - CSS MTA - JavaScript MTA - Database administration MTA - Software development MTA)

## MASTERING

- ✓ Agile
- ✓ Attention to details
- ✓ Ability to anticipate
- ✓ Team spirit
- ✓ Remote work
- ✓ Excellent analytical skills
- ✓ Sense of organization

## **INTERESTS**

- Chess.
- Swimming.
- Football.
- Photography.
- Camping.

# **LANGUAGES**

Arabic : Native language.

Frensh : Good level.

English : Medium.



Scan me!